That's sexy...
セクシーだなぁ...
Does it feel good here?
ここね、気持ちいい?
I need to wash it a bit...
ちょっと洗わないとね...
Tired...
疲れる...
I'm a little tired...
ちょっとお疲れです...
I can't think of what I just thought...
今考えた考えない...
It's always impossible...
いつも、いつも無理だよ...
I guess so...
そうかなぁ...
Isn't that so?
そうでしょ
...
What, aren't you hedging?
え、 ヘッジしてない?
No...
ないよ...
Who do you live with?
誰と住んでるの?
Is it too early?
お早すぎですかね?
お 早すぎですか?
Is it cold?
寒いの?
Close it...
閉めて...
cold...
寒い...
You have a pretty face...
きれいな顔してるもん...
cold...
寒い...
It was a bit cold...
ちょっと寒かった...
Wash it a little faster...
ちょっと早く洗って...
Isn't that how you sleep?
そんな寝てるんじゃない?
Thank you...
せっかく...
I don't get to see you very often...
なかなか会えないじゃん...
Shaved pussy is nice...
パイパンはいいね...
Not shaved...
パイパンにしてない...
This is a pop...
これポンじゃん...
Yes, but...
そうだけど...
That's right...
そうなんだけど...
I want you to wash this too...
ちょっとこれも洗ってほしい...
It's not wet so it's very slippery...
濡らしてないから滑りがとても悪い...
Eh, it doesn't foam...
えー、泡立たないなぁ...
This smells amazing...
すげーいい匂いするじゃんこれ...
Huh, what's that smell?
えー、何の匂いだろうね?
Orange or something?
オレンジとかか?
It's probably citrusy...
柑橘系だな、多分...
Isn't it ticklish?
くすぐったばんない?
It's not ticklish at all...
全然くすぐったばんない...
If it's a lotion or something...
ローションとかだとなるけど...
Something like this...
これなんか...
Because it doesn't slip...
滑りないから...
Because body soda...
だって、ボディソーダ...
Wouldn't it be a problem if it were lotion?
ローションだったら困るでしょ?
If it were lotion, it might start again...
ローションだったらまた始まっちゃうかもしれない...
Let's take a little break...
もう、ちょっと休憩...
break?
休 憩?
break!
休憩!
I haven't gotten wet in the shower, so it's not enough...
シャワー濡らしてないから足んないんだけど...
It's dangerous...
危険だ...
I need a break too...
ちょっとこれも休憩が必要だ...
I need a break...
休憩が必要だ...
If this really cheers me up...
これでさすがに元気が出たら本当に...
Physical strength idiot...
体力バカ...
I think you're an idiot for your physical strength...
体力バカだと思うの...
What is a physical strength idiot?
体力バカって何?
I have too much physical strength...
体力がありすぎるの...
Eh...
えー...
what?
何?
It's not just about physical strength...
体力だけじゃないよ...
So what do we have?
じゃあ何があるの?
It's love...
愛だね...
Love...
愛か...
Don't you feel refreshed?
パッとしないの?
Is it something that changes with love?
愛で変わるものなんですか?
It'll change...
変わるでしょ...
cute...
かわいい...
Long break...
長休みよ...
amazing...
すごい...
I don't know if I used Konkus, but...
コンクス使ったかわからないけど...
Tsubetsube...
ツベツベ...
Tsubetsube?
ツベツベ?
Well, it's starting to get sticky...
いや、ツベツベになってきましたけど...
Really?
本当に?
Isn't it boring...
ツベツベじゃないですか...
Well, this too...
じゃあ、これも...
I think I'll take it...
取ると思う...
Tsubetsube...
ツベツベ...
Oh, wait...
あ、待って...
thank you...
ありがとう...
wait a minute ...
ちょっと 待って ...
Isn't this the one below the heart?
これ、心の下ってやつやつじゃない?
what?
何?
Isn't that the one below?
下ってやつやつじゃない?
Don't you know?
分かんないかな?
Are you shiny?
テカテカしてる?
It's shiny...
テカテカしてる...
Isn't that broken?
あれは切れてないの?
Isn't that it?
それじゃないの?
I wonder if there's something in there?
あれ、何か入ってるのかな?
There's a good guy in there, it's a good hotel...
いいやつ入ってるね、いいホテルだから...
It smells like oranges, so there's some aroma and stuff in there too.
オレンジの匂いするからさ、 アロマとかそこら辺も入ってくる
...
Ah, I understand.
あー、 分かってん
of...
の...
Don't you have a helmet?
かぶとないの?
It's not cold at all...
全然、寒くない...
Well, why did you stay?
え、どうして残ったの?
It's not cold, is it?
寒くないよね
...
I'm looking at you all the time...
こん かわんぐるさら見ている...
That face...
あの、顔...
It's different, right?
違うよね?
picture?
え?
How do you see Suka-chan?
スカちゃんどう見てるの?
It's not cold...
寒くない...
Water will flow...
水が流れちゃうよ...
水 が流れちゃうね...
Let's talk for a while and then go eat...
ちょっと、喋ったらご飯食べていこうか...
It's fun...
楽しいね...
I hope it's delicious...
美味しいの期待してるからね...
interesting...
面白い...